Faculty of Arts fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Faculty of Arts fonds
1965 - 1984
F-2
4.88 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences
The Faculty of Arts was one of the three founding faculties of the University established in September 1965, as required by the Universities Act, 1963. c.52 (RS 1979, c. 419). According to the Act, a faculty has a number of powers and duties, including the responsibility to make rules for its self-governance; provide for student representation in faculty bodies and meetings; determine the courses of instruction offered and who is eligible to provide such instruction; appoint examiners to conduct examinations and determine results; and decide on all applications and memorials by students and others in connection with the Faculty. In addition to these powers, a faculty is the central intermediary body through which funding is disbursed to departments and non-departmental programs, including the provision of facilities, equipment and support. In keeping with the overall approach of the University, the Faculty of Arts has sought from its inception to foster interdisciplinary research and teaching.
The Faculty is organized administratively into a Dean of Arts, Associate Dean, and a number of faculty committees, including the committee of the whole. The Dean, as the chief officer and chair of the faculty committee, is responsible for ensuring that the varied duties and responsibilities of the Faculty are carried out. The position of Associate Dean, established in 1966, has been responsible for space allotment, the appointment of sessional staff, the coordination of curriculum development in graduate and undergraduate programs, advice to the Dean on specific matters, and to take the role of Acting Dean when required.
The number and composition of faculty standing committees has changed little over time. Those committees which have existed since the inception of the University include Academic Planning, Curriculum, Dean's Advisory, Graduate Studies, and Tenure. The Faculty has also had a number of ad hoc committees, which were numerous during the first developmental years of the Faculty. These included the Departmental Review and Grading committees.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body.
The fonds of the Faculty of Arts consists of records made and received in the course of the administration of the Faculty and the carrying out of its functions. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; approval of curriculum and program recommendations from departments; representation to the Senate and Board of Governors; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; and dispute resolution. The types of documents include meeting agenda and minutes, annual reports, correspondence, faculty files, memoranda, publications, reports, and working papers.
The records were arranged by the Archivist according to office of origin and subject.
Brown, Robert C.; Smith, W. A. S.; Sullivan, Dale; Mathews, John; MacPherson, Archibald; Bottomore, Tom B.; Cunningham, Allan B.; Munro, John M.
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Faculty in the early 1980s.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed as of September 2002 (3.67 m., 1974-1994). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventories of the Faculty of Arts departmental fonds.
Some access restrictions apply in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the the archivist.
File lists are available.
- Office of the Dean, 1965 - 1981; F-2-1; 1.66 m of textual records
  published
  The office of the Dean came into being with the establishment of the Faculty of Arts in September 1965. As the executive officer of the Faculty and an administrative officer of the University, the Dean has been responsible to the Senate for ensuring that the functions of the Faculty were carried out. Between 1965 and 1968, the position of Dean was filled in rotation between the Faculties of Arts and Science, and the responsibilities and duties of the position were limited to membership on the Committee of Heads, consisting of the President, Deans, and the heads of departments.
  On 1 March 1968, the Board of Governors approved the recommendation that the Dean be a permanent position and have more extensive duties. Specifically, the position was given six major duties: 1) to act as the central budget authority for all departments and programs in the Faculty of Arts; 2) to administer all Arts non-departmental programs; 3) to coordinate curriculum development through the faculty undergraduate and graduate curriculum committees and maintain scholastic uniformity; 4) to be responsible for faculty hiring, discipline, tenure and promotion in conjunction with appropriate departments; 5) to facilitate the research undertaken by faculty members by ensuring facilities, equipment and support, and; 6) to engage in the ongoing assessment of faculty performance, through performance review, contract renewal, tenure and promotion evaluations. Further, the Dean acts as chair of faculty meetings and represents the Faculty to external bodies such as the Senate and the Board of Governors.
  Series consists of records relating to the activities of the Dean as the chief officer of the Faculty. The records document both administrative and operational activities, including correspondence with university and external bodies and participation on various committees. The forms of materials include meeting agenda and minutes, correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  Access may be restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Dean's office, 1966 - 1980; F-2-1-1; 5 cm of textual records
    - Rules and procedures, 1966; F-2-1-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
      Textual records
      Pending review
    - Organizational review, 1976; F-2-1-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Position of Dean, 1966 - 1970; F-2-1-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Position of Dean, 1972 - 1980; F-2-1-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Departmental Chairmen, 1969 - 1978; F-2-1-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
  - General correspondence, 1965 - 1979; F-2-1-2; 49 cm of textual records
    For a list of correspondents, see Access Points.
    Board of Governors; Senate; Office of the President; Department of Archaeology; Department of Economics; Department of English; Department of Geography; Department of History; Department of Languages, Literature and Linguistics; Department of Political Science; Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology; Department of Philosophy; Department of Sociology and Anthropology; Department of Psychology; Institutional Research and Planning; University Bookstore; School for the Contemporary Arts; Computing Services; Continuing Studies; Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies; Centre for Online and Distance Education; Simon Fraser University Faculty Association; Faculty of Education; Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies; Faculty of Science; Financial Aid and Awards; University Library; Open Learning Institute; Human Resources; Simon Fraser Student Society; University Review Committee; Office of the Vice-President, Academic and Provost; Office of the Vice-President, Administration
    - Correspondence: B.O.G., 1974 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence: Senate, 1974 - 1975; F-2-1-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence: President, 1967 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1967; F-2-1-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, 1965; F-2-1-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, 1966; F-2-1-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, 1967; F-2-1-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, 1968; F-2-1-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-1)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, January 1969 - December 1969; F-2-1-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, 1970; F-2-1-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, 1971; F-2-1-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: memoranda, 1972 - 1975; F-2-1-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: Archaeology, 1968 - 1973; F-2-1-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: Economics, 1967 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: Economics, 1974 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: English, 1968 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 2-2)
    - Correspondence: Geography, 1970 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: History, 1971 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: Languages Literature and Linguistics, 1973 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: Political Science, 1974 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: Pol. Sc., Sociology and Anthropology, 1970; F-2-1-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: Philosophy, 1978 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: Psychology, 1971 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: Sociology and Anthropology, 1974 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 2-3)
    - Correspondence: Analytical Studies, 1975 - 1978; F-2-1-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Bookstore, 1972 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Centre for the Arts, 1972 - 1975; F-2-1-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Computing Centre, 1974 - 1975; F-2-1-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Continuing Studies, 1976 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Dean Graduate Stud., 1973 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Distance Education, 1978 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: External Universities Council, 1973 - 1977; F-2-1-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: External Universities Council, 1978 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Faculty Association, 1969 - 1971; F-2-1-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Education Faculty, 1969 - 1975; F-2-1-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Interdisciplinary Studies Faculty, 1972 - 1978; F-2-1-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Science Faculty, 1967 - 1978; F-2-1-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Financial Aid, 1977 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Legal Studies, 1976 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Library, 1973 - 1977; F-2-1-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Open Learning Institute, 1978 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Personnel, 1971 - 1977; F-2-1-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Student Society, 1974 - 1978; F-2-1-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: teaching assistants, 1972 - 1975; F-2-1-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: University Review Committee, 1976 - 1977; F-2-1-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 2-4)
    - Correspondence: Vice President Academic, 1970 - 1978; F-2-1-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Correspondence: Vice President Administration, 1970 - 1978; F-2-1-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Correspondence: Vice President Student Services, 1969 - 1979; F-2-1-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
  - Chronological correspondence, 1973 - 1980; F-2-1-3; 83 cm of textual records
    - Chronological correspondence, January 1973; F-2-1-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, February 1973; F-2-1-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, March 1973; F-2-1-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, April 1973; F-2-1-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, May 1973; F-2-1-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, June 1973; F-2-1-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, July 1973; F-2-1-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, August 1973; F-2-1-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, September 1973; F-2-1-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence (missing), October 1973 - December 1973; F-2-1-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-2-1-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 2-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-2-1-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 2-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-2-1-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-2-1-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 2-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 2-9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-2-1-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-76 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-77 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-78 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-79 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-80 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-81 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1979; F-2-1-3-0-82 (Archival box - standard 2-10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-83 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-84 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-85 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-86 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-87 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-88 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-89 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-90 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-91 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-92 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-93 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980; F-2-1-3-0-94 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
  - Subject files, 1967 - 1978; F-2-1-4; 14 cm of textual records
    University Review Committee
    - Average Cumulative G.P.A. of Graduands, 1967 - 1971; F-2-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - Contingency fund (samples only), 1970 - 1978; F-2-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-11)
    - New programs, 1971 - 1978; F-2-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - Pre-registration, 1969 - 1976; F-2-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - Referenda ballots (samples), 1977 - 1978; F-2-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - Student complaints, 1969 - 1977; F-2-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - Student grade appeals, 1973 - 1975; F-2-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - Student grade appeals, 1976; F-2-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - Student grade appeals, 1977 - 1978; F-2-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - Summer employment, 1974 - 1977; F-2-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
    - University Review Committee, 1977 - 1978; F-2-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-12)
  - Printed material and reports, 1966 - 1981; F-2-1-5; 15 cm of textual records
    - Report: Appeals for Grade Change, 1966 - 1969; F-2-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: Appeals for Grade Change, 1969 - 1971; F-2-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: Academic Advice Centre, 1975; F-2-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: Academic Advice Centre, 1979; F-2-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: Dean's Interview with Peak, 1976; F-2-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
      Open
    - Report: Organization Review of the Faculty of Arts, 1976; F-2-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: Post Grad Activities of 1976-77 S.F.U. Grads, 1979; F-2-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: Proposal for Reorganization of Office of Dean, 1974; F-2-1-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: History of Course Enrollment, 1971 - 1972; F-2-1-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: History of Course Enrollment, 1973 - 1974; F-2-1-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: History of Course Enrollment, 1975; F-2-1-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-13)
    - Report: History of Course Enrollment, 1979 - 1981; F-2-1-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-14)
    - Report: Course Offerings, 1976; F-2-1-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-14)
- Faculty Members, 1965 - 1979; F-2-2; 58 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records and case files relating to faculty members, including staffing, appointments, salary reviews, policies, and grievances. It includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, and staff lists. Case files of faculty members are arranged alphabetically within each subseries.
  - Subject files, 1965 - 1979; F-2-2-1; 18 cm of textual records
    - List of Chairmen and Heads, 1965 - 1973; F-2-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-14)
    - Faculty publications (Dept. of English), 1965 - 1977; F-2-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-14)
    - Faculty lists, 1969 - 1970; F-2-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-14)
    - Salary review, 1971 - 1979; F-2-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-14)
    - Faculty position requests, 1975 - 1976; F-2-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-14)
    - Staff appointments and policy, 1969 - 1975; F-2-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-14)